<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="eula_title">END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT</string>
	<string name="eula">
PleftDroid is now released under GPLv3, this is a template EULA in case you are re-distributing it on the market AND you want to include a EULA.
1. Introduction\n
This License is a Legal Agreement between You and the owner of the APPLICATIONNAME Android™ Application website at YOURWEBSITEHERE(if any) ( here after referered to as “Application Provider” ) for the use of the APPLICATIONNAME Android™ Application (here after referered to as “the Licensed Application”).\n
By downloading the Licensed Application from the Application Provider or Google™ Play Market (here after referered to as “The Market”), installing or using this application or any portion thereof (“Licensed Application”), you agree to the following terms and conditions (the “Terms and Conditions”) and
You accept to be bound to the Market terms of service as described on the Market web site ( http://www.google.com/mobile/android/market-tos.html ), which are subject to change without notice.\n
\n
2. Scope of License:\n
This license granted to You for the Licensed Application by the Application Provider is limited to a non-transferable license to use the Licensed Application on any Android™ device that You own or control and as permitted by the Usage Rules set forth in Section 3.b. of this License (the “Usage Rules”). This license does not allow You to distribute or make the Licensed Application available over a network where it could be used by multiple devices at the same time. You may not rent, lease, lend, sell, redistribute or sublicense the Licensed Application. You may not copy (except as expressly permitted by this license and the Usage Rules), decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, attempt to derive the source code of, modify, or create derivative works of the Licensed Application, any updates, or any part thereof (except as and only to the extent any foregoing restriction is prohibited by applicable law or to the extent as may be permitted by the licensing terms governing use of any open sourced components included with the Licensed Application). Any attempt to do so is a violation of the rights of the Application Provider and its licensors. If You breach this restriction, You may be subject to prosecution and damages. The terms of the license will govern any upgrades provided by Application Provider that replace and/or supplement the original Product, unless such upgrade is accompanied by a separate license in which case the terms of that license will govern.\n
\n
3. Use of The Licensed Application\n
a. The Application Provider grants you the non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited right and license to install and use this Application solely and exclusively for your personal use.\n
b. You may not use the Licensed Application in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the Licensed Application (or servers or networks connected to the Licensed Application), nor may you use the Licensed Application in any manner that could interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the Licensed Application (or servers or networks connected to the Licensed Application).\n
c. You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that the Application Provider has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) your use of the Licensed Application, any breach of your obligations under the Terms and Conditions, and for the consequences (including any loss or damage which The Application Provider may suffer) of any such breach.\n
\n
4. PROPRIETARY RIGHTS\n
You acknowledge that (a) the Licensed Application contains proprietary and confidential information that is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws, and (b) The Application Provider and/or third parties own all right, title and interest in and to the Licensed Application and content, excluding content provided by you, that may be presented or accessed through the Licensed Application, including without limitation all Intellectual Property Rights therein and thereto. “Intellectual Property Rights” means any and all rights existing from time to time under patent law, copyright law, trade secret law, trademark law, unfair competition law, and any and all other proprietary rights, and any and all applications, renewals, extensions and restorations thereof, now or hereafter in force and effect worldwide. You agree that you will not, and will not allow any third party to, (i) copy, sell, license, distribute, transfer, modify, adapt, translate, prepare derivative works from, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble or otherwise attempt to derive source code from the Licensed Application or content that may be presented or accessed through the Licensed Application for any purpose, unless otherwise permitted, (ii) take any action to circumvent or defeat the security or content usage rules provided, deployed or enforced by any functionality (including without limitation digital rights management functionality) contained in the Licensed Application, (iii) use the Licensed Application to access, copy, transfer, transcode or retransmit content in violation of any law or third party rights, or (iv) remove, obscure, or alter The Application Provider’s or any third party\'s copyright notices, trademarks, or other proprietary rights notices affixed to or contained within or accessed in conjunction with or through the Licensed Application.\n
\n
5. THE Market TERMS OF SERVICE AND PRIVACY POLICY
a. The Market\'s Privacy Policy (located at http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) explains how The Market treats your information and protects your privacy when you use the Licensed Application. You agree to the use of your data in accordance with The Market’s privacy policies.
b. the Licensed Application may contain features that are used in conjunction with The Market’s search and other services. Accordingly, your use of such features of the Licensed Application is also governed by The Market’s Terms of Service located at http://www.google.com/mobile/android/market-tos.html, The Market’s Privacy Policy located at http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html, as well as any applicable The Market Service-specific Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, which may be updated from time to time and without notice.\n
\n
6. U.S. GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS\n
This Application, related materials and documentation have been developed entirely with private funds. If the user of the Licensed Application is an agency, department, employee, or other entity of the United States Government, the use, duplication, reproduction, release, modification, disclosure, or transfer of the Licensed Application, including technical data or manuals, is restricted by the terms, conditions and covenants contained in these Terms and Conditions. In accordance with Federal Acquisition Regulation 12.212 for civilian agencies and Defense Federal Acquisition Regulation Supplement 227.7202 for military agencies, use of the Licensed Application is further restricted by these Terms and Conditions.\n
\n
7. EXPORT RESTRICTIONS\n
the Licensed Application may be subject to export controls or restrictions by the United States or other countries or territories. You agree to comply with all applicable U.S. and international export laws and regulations. These laws include restrictions on destinations, end users, and end use.\n
\n
8. TERMINATION\n
These Terms and Conditions will continue to apply until terminated by either you or the Application Provider as set forth below. You may terminate these Terms and Conditions at any time by permanently deleting the Licensed Application from your mobile device in its entirety. Your rights automatically and immediately terminate without notice from the Application Provider or any Third Party if you fail to comply with any provision of these Terms and Conditions. In such event, you must immediately delete the Licensed Application.\n
\n
9. INDEMNITY\n
To the maximum extent permitted by law, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless the Application Provider, its affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against any and all claims, actions, suits or proceedings, as well as any and all losses, liabilities, damages, costs and expenses (including reasonable attorneys fees) arising out of or accruing from your use of the Licensed Application, including your downloading, installation, or use of the Licensed Application, or your violation of these Terms and Conditions.\n
\n
10. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES\n
a. YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE LICENSED APPLICATION IS AT YOUR SOLE DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED AS IS AND AS AVAILABLE WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.\n
b. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, OR OTHER DEVICE, OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM SUCH USE.\n
c. THE APPLICATION PROVIDER FURTHER EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE APPLICATION.\n
d. THE APPLICATION IS NOT INTENDED FOR USE IN THE OPERATION OF NUCLEAR FACILITIES, LIFE SUPPORT SYSTEMS, EMERGENCY COMMUNICATIONS, AIRCRAFT NAVIGATION OR COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS, AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL SYSTEMS, OR ANY OTHER ACTIVITIES IN WHICH THE FAILURE OF THE APPLICATION COULD LEAD TO DEATH, PERSONAL INJURY, OR SEVERE PHYSICAL OR ENVIRONMENTAL DAMAGE.\n
\n
11. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT THE APPLICATION PROVIDER, ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATES, AND ITS LICENSORS ARE NOT LIABLE TO YOU UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES THAT MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE APPLICATION, INCLUDING ANY LOSS OF DATA OR DAMAGE TO YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, WHETHER OR NOT THE APPLICATION PROVIDER OR ITS REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE BEEN AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH LOSSES ARISING.\n
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THIS LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. In no event shall Application Provider’s total liability to you for all damages (other than as may be required by applicable law in cases involving personal injury) exceed the amount of twenty dollars ($20.00). The foregoing limitations will apply even if the above stated remedy fails of its essential purpose.
	</string>
</resources>
